http://www.follettice.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Visiting from Europe?
Privacy Policy
Follett takes your privacy seriously.  To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  To make this notice easy to find, we make a link available on every page throughout our website.
The following policy outlines how Follett handles any information we collect from you during your visit to our website.  Please check this policy periodically because we may modify it at any time without notice.
How we handle your information
Personal information submitted by you to Follett's website, or collected by Follett as a result of your visit to our website, will be considered private and held in confidence.   We will not sell, share, distribute or rent this information to any third parties.
In order to complete a transaction, such as request information from Follett (price quotes, product information, or a site evaluation), purchase spare parts or equipment, request technical support or register a warranty, or sign up for one of Follett's technical training seminars, a user must provide certain information.  This information may include name, address, phone number and email address, billing information and/or credit card information .  This information is used to contact the user, to fulfill the user's request, and to process the user's order.  Credit card numbers and expiration dates are used only for payment processing and are not retained following successful completion of the transaction.
In order to tailor subsequent communications to you and to continuously improve our products and services, we may ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding products of interest and your contact preferences.  From time to time we may use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with marketing information we think would be of particular interest.  We will always give you the ability to opt out of receiving future communications such as these.
Follett's website utilizes cookies to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site, unless you separately supply the information to us yourself (such as by submitting a request form).  A cookie cannot read the data off your hard drive, or read cookie files created by other sites.  The cookie can tell us that the same computer has visited our website in the past, or that a visitor arrived at our website by following a link that we placed in an advertisement, but it cannot tell us any identifying information such as your name or your location.  You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.  By doing so you can still use Follett's website, but some parts of the website may not function properly.
Follett uses IP addresses to analyze trends in website usage, administer the site, track user's movements throughout the website and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Follett is committed to ensuring the security of your information.  To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  For example, we use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information, and only those personnel whose specific job functions require access to personally identifiable information are granted access.
contact us
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us:
800-523-9361 (U.S. only)
Back to top
Back to top
We use cookies on this site to enhance your user experience. Click here for more information.
Dismiss
